Guide to the Civil War Stereographs 1861-1865 PR 65-1
New-York Historical Society
- Engine house in which John Brown was captured., 1865 (Item 815-8)
  Brick building with rounded windows, lookout tower on roof.
- Engine house fortified by John Brown at Harper's Ferry, Va., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 815-9)